<resources>
    <!-- string awal bawaan -->
    <string name="app_name">Sub-2-Azwar</string>

    <!-- ini buat translate -->
    <string name="tab_movie">Movie</string>
    <string name="tab_tvshow">TV Show</string>
    <string name="change_language">Change Language</string>
    <string name="txt_overview">Overview</string>
    <string name="txt_release_date">Release</string>
    <string name="txt_language">Language</string>
    <string name="txt_title">Title</string>
    <string name="txt_creator">Creator</string>
    <string name="txt_status">Status</string>

    <string name="ov_a_star">
        Seasoned musician Jackson Maine discovers - and falls in love with - struggling artist Ally.
        She has just about given up on her dream to make it big as a singer - until Jack coaxes her into the spotlight.
        But even as Ally\'s career takes off, the personal side of their relationship is breaking down,
        as Jack fights an ongoing battle with his own internal demons.
    </string>

    <string name="ov_aquamen">
        Once home to the most advanced civilization on Earth, Atlantis is now an underwater kingdom ruled by the power-hungry King Orm.
        With a vast army at his disposal, Orm plans to conquer the remaining oceanic people and then the surface world.
        Standing in his way is Arthur Curry, Orm\'s half-human, half-Atlantean brother and true heir to the throne.
    </string>

    <string name="ov_avenger">
        As the Avengers and their allies have continued to protect the world from threats too large for any one hero to handle,
        a new danger has emerged from the cosmic shadows: Thanos. A despot of intergalactic infamy, his goal is to collect all six Infinity Stones,
        artifacts of unimaginable power, and use them to inflict his twisted will on all of reality.
        Everything the Avengers have fought for has led up to this moment - the fate of Earth and existence itself has never been more uncertain.
    </string>

    <string name="ov_glass">
        In a series of escalating encounters, former security guard David Dunn uses his supernatural abilities to track Kevin Wendell Crumb,
        a disturbed man who has twenty-four personalities. Meanwhile, the shadowy presence of Elijah Price emerges as an orchestrator who holds secrets critical to both men.
    </string>

    <string name="ov_hunter_killer">
        Captain Glass of the USS Arkansas discovers that a coup d\'etat is taking place in Russia,
        so he and his crew join an elite group working on the ground to prevent a war.
    </string>
    <string name="ov_marry">
        In Depression-era London, a now-grown Jane and Michael Banks, along with Michael\'s three children,
        are visited by the enigmatic Mary Poppins following a personal loss. Through her unique magical skills,
        and with the aid of her friend Jack, she helps the family rediscover the joy and wonder missing in their lives.
    </string>

    <string name="ov_robin">
        A war-hardened Crusader and his Moorish commander mount an audacious revolt against the corrupt English crown.
    </string>

    <string name="ov_the_girl">
        In Stockholm, Sweden, hacker Lisbeth Salander is hired by Frans Balder, a computer engineer, to retrieve a program that he believes it is too dangerous to exist.
    </string>

    <string name="ov_the_mule">
        Earl Stone, a man in his eighties, is broke, alone, and facing foreclosure of his business when he is offered a job that simply requires him to drive.
        Easy enough, but, unbeknownst to Earl, he\'s just signed on as a drug courier for a Mexican cartel. He does so well that his cargo increases exponentially,
        and Earl hit the radar of hard-charging DEA agent Colin Bates.
    </string>

    <string name="ov_deadpool">
        A kidnapped Fred Savage is forced to endure Deadpool\'s PG-13 rendition of Deadpool 2 as a Princess Bride-esque story that\'s full of magic, wonder and zero F\'s.
    </string>

    <string-array name="data_title_film">
        <item>A Star Is born</item>
        <item>Aquaman</item>
        <item>Avengers : Infinity War</item>
        <item>Glass</item>
        <item>Hunter Killer</item>
        <item>Mary Poppins Returns</item>
        <item>Robin Hood</item>
        <item>The Girl in The Spider\'s Web</item>
        <item>The Mule</item>
        <item>Once Upon a Deadpool</item>
    </string-array>

    <array name="data_poster_film">
        <item>@drawable/poster_a_star</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_aquaman</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_infinity_war</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_glass</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_hunterkiller</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_marrypopins</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_robinhood</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_thegirl</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_themule</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_deadpool</item>
    </array>

    <string-array name="data_overview_film">
        <item>@string/ov_a_star</item>
        <item>@string/ov_aquamen</item>
        <item>@string/ov_avenger</item>
        <item>@string/ov_glass</item>
        <item>@string/ov_hunter_killer</item>
        <item>@string/ov_marry</item>
        <item>@string/ov_robin</item>
        <item>@string/ov_the_girl</item>
        <item>@string/ov_the_mule</item>
        <item>@string/ov_deadpool</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="data_tahun_film">
        <item>2018</item>
        <item>2018</item>
        <item>2018</item>
        <item>2019</item>
        <item>2018</item>
        <item>2018</item>
        <item>2018</item>
        <item>2018</item>
        <item>2018</item>
        <item>2018</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="data_bahasa_film">
        <item>English</item>
        <item>English</item>
        <item>English</item>
        <item>English</item>
        <item>English</item>
        <item>English</item>
        <item>English</item>
        <item>English</item>
        <item>English</item>
        <item>English</item>
    </string-array>
    <!-- movie sampe sini-->

    <!-- lanjut yang tv shownye-->
    <string name="ov_grey_an">
        Follows the personal and professional lives of a group of doctors at Seattle\’s Grey Sloan Memorial Hospital.
    </string>

    <string name="ov_supernatural">
        When they were boys, Sam and Dean Winchester lost their mother to a mysterious and demonic supernatural force. Subsequently, their father raised them to be soldiers.
        He taught them about the paranormal evil that lives in the dark corners and on the back roads of America . and he taught them how to kill it. Now,
        the Winchester brothers crisscross the country in their \'67 Chevy Impala, battling every kind of supernatural threat they encounter along the way.
    </string>

    <string name="ov_ncis">
        From murder and espionage to terrorism and stolen submarines, a team of special agents investigates any
        crime that has a shred of evidence connected to Navy and Marine Corps personnel, regardless of rank or position.
    </string>

    <string name="ov_hana">
        This thriller and coming-of-age drama follows the journey of an extraordinary young girl as she evades the
        relentless pursuit of an off-book CIA agent and tries to unearth the truth behind who she is. Based on the 2011 Joe Wright film.
    </string>

    <string name="ov_marvels_iron">
        Danny Rand resurfaces 15 years after being presumed dead. Now, with the power of the Iron Fist, he seeks to reclaim his past and fulfill his destiny.
    </string>

    <string name="ov_the_simpsons">
        Set in Springfield, the average American town, the show focuses on the antics and everyday adventures of the Simpson family, Homer, Marge, Bart, Lisa and Maggie,
        as well as a virtual cast of thousands. Since the beginning, the series has been a pop culture icon, attracting
        hundreds of celebrities to guest star. The show has also made name for itself in its fearless satirical take on politics, media and American life in general.
    </string>

    <string name="ov_dragon_ball">
        Long ago in the mountains, a fighting master known as Gohan discovered a strange boy whom he named Goku. Gohan raised him and trained Goku in martial arts until he died.
        The young and very strong boy was on his own, but easily managed. Then one day, Goku met a teenage girl named Bulma,
        whose search for the mystical Dragon Balls brought her to Goku\'s home. Together, they set off to find all seven and to grant her wish.
    </string>

    <string name="ov_naruto">
        Naruto Shippuuden is the continuation of the original animated TV series Naruto.The story revolves around an older and slightly
        more matured Uzumaki Naruto and his quest to save his friend Uchiha Sasuke from the grips of the snake-like Shinobi, Orochimaru.
        After 2 and a half years Naruto finally returns to his village of Konoha, and sets about putting his ambitions to work,
        though it will not be easy, as He has amassed a few (more dangerous) enemies, in the likes of the shinobi organization. Akatsuki.
    </string>

    <string name="ov_doom_patrol">
        The Doom Patrol\’s members each suffered horrible accidents that gave them superhuman abilities - but also left them scarred
        and disfigured. Traumatized and downtrodden, the team found purpose through The Chief,
        who brought them together to investigate the weirdest phenomena in existence - and to protect Earth from what they find.
    </string>

    <string name="ov_family_guy">
        Sick, twisted, politically incorrect and Freakin\' Sweet animated series featuring the adventures of the dysfunctional Griffin family.
        Bumbling Peter and long-suffering Lois have three kids. Stewie (a brilliant but sadistic baby bent on killing his mother and taking over the world),
        Meg (the oldest, and is the most unpopular girl in town) and Chris (the middle kid, he\'s not very bright but has a passion for movies).
        The final member of the family is Brian - a talking dog and much more than a pet, he keeps Stewie in check whilst sipping Martinis and sorting through his own life issues.
    </string>

    <string-array name="data_ov_tvshow">
        <item>@string/ov_grey_an</item>
        <item>@string/ov_supernatural</item>
        <item>@string/ov_ncis</item>
        <item>@string/ov_hana</item>
        <item>@string/ov_marvels_iron</item>
        <item>@string/ov_the_simpsons</item>
        <item>@string/ov_dragon_ball</item>
        <item>@string/ov_naruto</item>
        <item>@string/ov_doom_patrol</item>
        <item>@string/ov_family_guy</item>

    </string-array>
    <string-array name="data_title_tvshow">
        <item>Grey\’s anatomy (2005)</item>
        <item>Supernatural (2005)</item>
        <item>NCIS (2003)</item>
        <item>Hana (2019)</item>
        <item>Marvels Iron Fist (2017)</item>
        <item>The Simpsons (1989)</item>
        <item>Dragon Ball</item>
        <item>Naruto Shippuden (2007)</item>
        <item>Doom Patrol (2019)</item>
        <item>Family Guy(1999)</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="data_creator_tvshow">
        <item>Shonda Rhimes</item>
        <item>Eric Kripkea</item>
        <item>Don McGill</item>
        <item>David Farr</item>
        <item>Scott Buck</item>
        <item>Matt Groening</item>
        <item>Akira Toriyama</item>
        <item>-</item>
        <item>Jeremy Carver</item>
        <item>Seth MacFarlane</item>
    </string-array>

    <array name="data_poster_tv">
        <item>@drawable/poster_grey_anatomy</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_supernatural</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_ncis</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_hanna</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_iron_fist</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_the_simpson</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_dragon_ball</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_naruto_shipudden</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_doom_patrol</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_family_guy</item>
    </array>

    <string-array name="data_status">
        <item>Running Series</item>
        <item>Running series</item>
        <item>Returning series</item>
        <item>Returning series</item>
        <item>Canceled</item>
        <item>Returning Series</item>
        <item>Ended</item>
        <item>Ended</item>
        <item>Returning Series</item>
        <item>Returning Series</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>
